<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects | Zhuo Chen</title>
    <link>https://zhuochen-ucla.github.io/project/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://zhuochen-ucla.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Projects</description>
    <generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://zhuochen-ucla.github.io/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>https://zhuochen-ucla.github.io/project/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explore Your Universe</title>
      <link>https://zhuochen-ucla.github.io/project/out1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhuochen-ucla.github.io/project/out1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have been one of the committee coordinators for 5 years on the largest annual science outreach event on campus: ​Exploring Your Universe. It is an inter-departmental public science outreach fair that is held in November every year, and attracts thousands of members to the UCLA campus.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Exploring Your Universe was founded in 2009 by graduate students in UCLA’s Astronomy department, and is now organized by volunteer graduate students representing several UCLA departments. This largest science outreach event on campus helps to bring scientific knowledge to our community free of charge.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Astronomy Live!</title>
      <link>https://zhuochen-ucla.github.io/project/example/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://zhuochen-ucla.github.io/project/example/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As a graduate student at UCLA astronomy department, I have been serving for 3 years as the coordinator leader for “Astronomy Live!” program, which is an astronomy outreach organization providing science demos and astronomy demonstrations to schools in the Los Angeles community. We have worked on organizing, coordinating and volunteering the outreach events to visit local schools or invite them to the UCLA campus. I hope to share my passion for science and astronomy through scientific outreach and education to interact with the community.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
